Oh, I should probably get going.
(Leonard:)-Come on, it's just a cup of coffee.
-Yeah. Okay.
[WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
(Howard(to Raj, who has whispered to him):)Yeah, the whole thing
seems a little twisted to me too.
(Leonard:)What am I smelling?
(Penny:)Sheldon's churro on my shoes.
(Penny:)Such an angel when he's asleep.
(Leonard:)Yeah, shame he has to wake up.
(Penny:)I think we can do it.
(Leonard:)Smother Sheldon in his sleep?
Wouldn't that be wrong?
(Penny:)No, be friends. You and me.
(Leonard:)Oh, sure.
(Leonard:)Absolutely.
(Sheldon:)Good. I'm glad.
(Leonard:)Here's an idea. I'm just throwing it
out there. Friends who have sex.
(Penny:)Good night, Leonard.
(Leonard:)Kidding. Just a couple of friends
goofing around.
(Sheldon(in his sleep):)No, Goofy, no.